{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043839222","data":{"timestamp":" 947043839222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043849716","data":{"timestamp":" 947043849716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043849950","data":{"timestamp":" 947043849949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043850927","data":{"timestamp":" 947043850927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043852215","data":{"timestamp":" 947043852214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043855087","data":{"timestamp":" 947043855086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043855943","data":{"timestamp":" 947043855942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043856265","data":{"timestamp":" 947043856265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043857510","data":{"timestamp":" 947043857510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043861089","data":{"timestamp":" 947043861089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043862088","data":{"timestamp":" 947043862087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043862351","data":{"timestamp":" 947043862350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043863301","data":{"timestamp":" 947043863300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043866245","data":{"timestamp":" 947043866245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043867289","data":{"timestamp":" 947043867289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043867770","data":{"timestamp":" 947043867770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043872311","data":{"timestamp":" 947043872310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043872402","data":{"timestamp":" 947043872401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" b1282da0-b28d-4248-90df-c0a45762e965"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043892585","data":{"timestamp":" 947043892585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sasa_pesa_sasa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043900007","data":{"timestamp":" 947043900007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sasa_pesa_sasa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043910531","data":{"timestamp":" 947043910530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sasa_pesa_sasa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043916721","data":{"timestamp":" 947043916721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" lisa_pesa_palesa_lisa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043923318","data":{"timestamp":" 947043923318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_pesa_nosisa_palesa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043930839","data":{"timestamp":" 947043930839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_pesa_nosisa_palesa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043937445","data":{"timestamp":" 947043937445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_sasa_palesa_elsa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043944050","data":{"timestamp":" 947043944050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" elsa_elsa_rosa_sasa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043951454","data":{"timestamp":" 947043951454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" elsa_elsa_rosa_sasa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043958051","data":{"timestamp":" 947043958051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_palesa_kosa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043964682","data":{"timestamp":" 947043964682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_elsa_makosa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043971269","data":{"timestamp":" 947043971269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" pesa_sasa_rosa_pesa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043977897","data":{"timestamp":" 947043977897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" pesa_sasa_pesa_lisa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043985365","data":{"timestamp":" 947043985365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" pesa_sasa_pesa_lisa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043994359","data":{"timestamp":" 947043994358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" 6f70ec38-6fc5-4b4c-8da4-227a16e9209e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pesa_sasa_pesa_lisa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044009655","data":{"timestamp":" 947044009655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" f6bbdca4-ca0b-4d49-8d51-b4da5f40e2e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044020381","data":{"timestamp":" 947044020381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" f6bbdca4-ca0b-4d49-8d51-b4da5f40e2e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044030577","data":{"timestamp":" 947044030577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_064233"," gameId":" f6bbdca4-ca0b-4d49-8d51-b4da5f40e2e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}